Hi there, I'm Tracy Goodwin and I'm the red sweater lady and today we're going to be talking about; how to improve perception.
Well how to improve perception of what?
Well people, places, things, ideas.
What is perception?
Perception is how you think and feel about things, people, places, ideas and in order to be a successful interpersonal communicator which is what we all strive for, we have to learn to improve our perception.
Perception can get in the way of our communication.
It can get in the way of our relationships.
With loved ones, with husbands and wives, with co-workers, with bosses, with everybody that we come in to, in to contact with.
Some people will tell you right away that they have really good perception.
They can really, they're really right about people when they first meet them and other people will say, oh I have terrible perception, I mean I always judge people wrong.
Well there's actually some things that you can do, some things that you can be aware of to help you improve your perception which will then in turn improve your interpersonal relationships.